

amy.hanv@gmail.com +1 (604) 902 6111 github.com/amyhanv 1102-728 Yates St, Victoria BC, V8W0C8

A software developer with strong communication and organizational skills and B.Sc. in Computer Science with a focus in front-end development and eye for design. Experienced in developing full-stack web applications and front-end React components and web pages to match design mock-ups. Comfortable with Agile methodologies and remote work.

# Work Experience

### Junior Software Developer

Dyspatch

Feb 2020 - Present Victoria, BC

- Develop new features on Dyspatch in a full-stack manner, adding new components and UI updates (React, Typescript) to adding back-end endpoints (Golang) and database migrations (SQL).
  - Integrate Stripe to support purchasing a subscription within Dyspatch.
- Implement front-end and back-end unit (Jest and Golang), integration, and E2E tests (Cypress) when working on a new feature or fixing a bug, prioritize test coverage to catch any future regressions.
- Collaborate closely with the design team to develop smooth and beautiful UI, vigilant for improvements in userexperience, and implementing components to match design mockups.
- Participate in cross-team meetings in feature scoping for upcoming tasks and Epics with technical owners to plan and prioritize the Agile technical roadmap.
- Lead team meetings over Zoom and take the initiative to coordinate any meetings with team members and designers to discuss technical implementations and UI.
- Write clear documentations for technical decisions, meetings, pull requests, and Asana task descriptions and notes.

**Developer**Co-op | May 2019 - Aug 2019

Wictoria, BC

- Developed the Momentum "New Tab" Chrome extension with over 3 million downloads and user-facing
- Built modular, reusable Vue and Backbone components with industry best practices for scalability and maintainability.
- Implemented automated testing for application functionality, design, and behaviour with Cypress.
- Created API endpoints and DB model (SQL) to save user feedback submissions.
- Collaborated in an Agile team environment with daily Scrum meetings.

### Involvements

#### President

Sept 2017 - Jan 2020

UVic WebDev Club

Organized clubs meetings and workshops

Momentum Team, using Vue and BackboneJS.

- Mentored club members with their projects, questions, or concerns
- Arranged hackathons and club events (e.g. HackUVic, HackathingUVic, UVic Spookathon, FiresideChat, etc.)
- Managed club group, website, social medias, and communications

## Education

#### **BSc Computer Science**

Sept 2014 - Jan 2020

University of Victoria

- Software Engineering Option
- Co-ops
- Relevant coursework:
  - Data Visualization, Databases, Computer
     Communications & Networks, Human-Computer
     Interaction, Documentation